<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dog Sounds with Details</string>

    <string name="atika_details_1">The Akita is a medium breed of dog
        originating from the mountainous regions of northern
        Japan. There are two separate varieties of Akita: a Japanese
        strain, commonly called "Akita Inu", or "Japanese Akita"; and 
        an American strain, known as the "Akita" or "American Akita"</string>

    <string name="boxer_dog_details_2">The Boxer is a medium-sized,
        short-haired breed of dog, developed in Germany.
        The coat is smooth and tight-fitting; colors are fawn brindled
        or white, with or without white markings.</string>

    <string name="cocker_spaniel_details_3">The English Cocker Spaniel is a breed of gun
        dog. It is noteworthy for producing one of the most varied
        numbers of pups in a litter among all dog breeds.
        The English Cocker Spaniel is an active, good-natured,
        sporting dog standing well
        up at the withers and compactly built.</string>
    <string name="doberman_dog_details_4">The Dobermann, or Doberman
        Pinscher dog that was originally developed around 1890
        by Karl Friedrich Louis Dobermann, a tax collector from Germany.
        The Dobermann has a long muzzle.It stands
        on its pads and is not usually heavy-footed.</string>

    <string name="german_shepher_details_5">The German Shepherd is a
        breed of medium to large sized working dog that originated in Germany.
        In the English language, the breed s officially recognized
        name is German Shepherd Dog. </string>

    <string name="labrador_detalis_6">The Labrador Retriever, or just
        Labrador, is a large type of retriever-gun dog. The Labrador
        is one of the most popular breeds of dog in Canada,
        the United Kingdom and the United States.</string>
    <string name="pomeranian_details_7">The Pomeranian is a breed ofdog of
        the Spitz type that is named for the Pomerania region in
        north-west Poland and north-east Germany in Central Europe.
        Classed as a toy dog breed because of its small size,
        the Pomeranian is descended
        from the larger Spitz-type dogs, specifically
        the German Spitz.</string>
    <string name="sheep_dog_details_8">A sheep dog or sheepdog is
        generally a dog or breed of dogs historically used in connection
        with the raising of sheep. These may include livestock guardian
        or pastoral dogs used to guard sheep and other livestock in farms for farmers,
        and herding dogs used to herd sheep and other livestock.</string>
    <string name="siberian_husky_details_9">The Siberian Husky is a
        medium size working dog breed that originated in Northeast Asia.
        The breed belongs to the Spitz genetic family.
        With proper training, they make great sled dogs.</string>
    <string name="pointer_dog_10">The Pointer, often called the English
        Pointer, is a medium to large-sized breed of dog, developed in
        England as a gun dog. It is one of several pointing breeds.</string>
    <string name="bulldog_details_11">The Bulldog, also known as the
        British Bulldog or English Bulldog, is a medium-sized breed of dog.
        It is a muscular, hefty dog with a wrinkled face and a
        distinctive pushed-in nose. The American
        Kennel Club,The Kennel Club,
        and the United Kennel Club oversee breeding records.</string>

    <string name="pub_dog_details_12">The pug is a breed of dog with
        physically distinctive features of a wrinkly, short-muzzled face,
        and curled tail. The breed has a fine,
        glossy coat that comes in a variety of colours,
        most often fawn or black,
        and a compact square body with well-developed muscles.</string>


    <string name="american_pitbull_details_13">The American Pit Bull Terrier is a purebred dog
        breed recognized by the United Kennel Club and American Dog
        Breeders Association, but not the American Kennel Club</string>

    <string name="rottweiler_details_14">The Rottweiler is a breed of
        domestic dog, regarded as medium-to-large or large.
        The dogs were known in German as Rottweiler.</string>

    <string name="chihuahua_dog_details_15">The Chihuahua is the smallest
        breed of dog and is named after the state of Chihuahua in Mexico.
        Chihuahuas possess a wide variety
        of four colors and coat thicknesses.</string>






</resources>
